{
  "quiz": {
    "questions": [
      {
        "prompt": "What game do Chris and Joel play?",
        "answer": "Ingress",
        "options": ["Candy Crush", "Pokemon Go", 2048]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "Where is Joel from?",
        "answer": "Texas",
        "options": ["New Mexico", "New York", "Massachusetts"]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "Where would Chris and Joel like to travel?",
        "answer": "Yellowstone",
        "options": ["Grand Canyon", "Yucatan Peninsula", "Mt Kilimanjaro"]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "What is the first car Chris and Joel bought together?",
        "answer": "2003 Mazda Protege",
        "options": ["2010 Mazda 3", "2004 Honda CRV", "2012 Jeep"]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "How many kids does Joel have?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [2, 1, 4]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "How many kids does Chris have?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [3, 0, 8]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "What fruit does Joel dislike?",
        "answer": "Bananas",
        "options": ["Apples", "Oranges", "Pears"]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "What fruit does Joel dislike?",
        "answer": "Bananas",
        "options": ["Apples", "Oranges", "Pears"]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "What fruit does Chris dislike?",
        "answer": "Blueberries",
        "options": ["Strawberries", "Oranges", "Pears"]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "What musical instrument does Chris play?",
        "answer": "None",
        "options": ["Guitar", "Keyboard", "Chimes"]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "Where was Chris and Joel's first date?",
        "answer": "Ruby Tuesday",
        "options": ["Chili's", "5 Guys", "Erbert & Gerbert's"]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "Where did Joel propose to Chris?",
        "answer": "Stone Arch Bridge",
        "options": ["IDS Crystal Court", "Newell Park", "Hudson Park"]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "How long was Chris and Joel's engagement?",
        "answer": "5 1/2 months",
        "options": ["7 months", "13 months", "10 1/2 months"]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "How much does the average wedding in Minnesota cost?",
        "answer": "$19k",
        "options": ["$7k", "$35k", "$10k"]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "The most sought after wedding month is?",
        "answer": "May",
        "options": ["November", "August", "July"]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "Where is Chris and Joel's new house?",
        "answer": "Hudson",
        "options": ["Stillwater", "River Falls", "Minneapolis"]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "Where is Chris and Joel's new house?",
        "answer": "Hudson",
        "options": ["Stillwater", "River Falls", "Minneapolis"]
      }
    ]
  }
}
